luckyvitamin.com 2016-05-12

# Privacy Policy - LuckyVitamin

At LuckyVitamin.com we protect your privacy as if it were our own. We use the information you provide to us for three purposes only: to process your order(s), to reply to your questions and provide our newsletter via email, and to incorporate your feedback into improvements to our Web site. We will not give, sell, or rent your personal information or specific account activity to anyone for any reason except as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.

## Our Secure Ordering

LuckyVitamin.com. uses Secured Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to ensure the privacy of your personal information. When you make an online purchase, our advanced security technology encrypts and scrambles your personal data (including your name, delivery and e-mail addresses and credit card number) before it is sent to us, making it virtually impossible for anyone other than LuckyVitamin.com, Inc. to read it. To further protect your information, we utilize the security. In addition, unless specifically authorized by you, no outside party is able to access or receive any of your personal customer information. 

To make sure you are accessing our secure server before you submit personal financial information, look at the lower left corner of your browser. If you see an unbroken key or a closed lock (depending upon your browser), the SSL is active. To double-check for security, look at the location line or your browser. If you have accessed a secure server, the first characters of the address in that line should change from "http" to "https." Some browser versions and some firewalls do not permit communication through a secure server like the ones we use at LuckyVitamin.com. If for any reason you cannot access the secure server, please feel free to place your order with us by phone at 1-888-635-0474 or you can fax or mail in your order using our printable order form. It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer. At LuckyVitamin.com we want you to feel completely comfortable. If you have more questions about our security systems, please call 1-888-635-0474 and we will be happy to help you.

## Credit Card Fraud Protection

All major credit card companies protect cardholders against fraud, subject to a $50 deductible. LuckyVitamin.com will protect you for this $50 portion in the highly unlikely situation that you ever encounter an inappropriate charge involving our company.

## Optional Phone, Fax & Mail Ordering

If you are still skeptical about placing your order online, you may place your order over the phone at 1-888-635-0474, via fax at 610-635-0472 or mail your order in and we will process your order during normal business hours Monday-Friday when we receive it. If you are going to mail an order in to fax it please print out the Printable Order Form. 

## Information We Collect

When you visit our web site, we collect non-personal information about your visit. We collect your IP address, browser type, domain name, and we log the length of time of your visit and the number of times you visit and purchase from us. We assign you a unique internal identifier to help keep track of your future visits. We use this information to gather aggregate demographic information about our visitors, and we use it to personalize the information you see on our web site and the emails you receive from us (should you grant us permission to send to you). We keep this information for our internal use; we do not share it with others. This information is in no way tied to your personal information. 

When you subscribe to our newsletters or submit a question to our "Professional Support Section ", LuckyVitamin.com., asks you for contact information (your name and email address). When you sign up for our newsletter we use your name and email address to send you our health newsletter and to inform you of sales and special offers. When you submit a question to "Professional Support " we will use your email address to send you the answer to your question and for no other purpose.

Recommend product to a friend. The information collected (friend's name and email address) is used to send a one time only email to the friend letting them know about the product that the user recommends.

If you place an online order, our secure order form requests contact, billing, and financial information (such as your credit card numbers for purchases). Contact information from the order form (email address, name, billing and shipping address, and phone number) is used to send orders and information about our company to you. Your contact information is also used to get in touch with you should we have questions regarding your order or should we need to notify you of the status of your order. And yes, you can opt not to get email from us, as described in the opt-out section below. The credit card information we collect is used ONLY to bill you for products you purchase. You will automatically be registered to receive our e-newsletter unless you opt-out at the time of purchase. You may opt-out at any later time by following the unsubscribe instructions in the newsletter.

## Third-party relationships.

1\. We use third-party intermediaries. When you purchase from us, we send your credit card information, name, and billing address to credit card companies for verification and to authorize your purchase.  
2\. We use outside shipping companies to fulfill delivery of orders. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any other purposes. 

We occasionally run our own online surveys and we ask visitors for contact information (such as email address) and demographic information (such as zip code, age, or income level). We use contact data from our surveys to send users information about our company. You may opt-out of the survey and also opt-out of any future mailings at the time of the survey. The demographic information is used to learn more about the types of people who visit our site. This information is not shared with any other parties currently. We reserve the right to share this information with other parties in the future in an aggregated format that would not disclose any personally identifiable information.

## Opt-Out

If you decide to opt out of our newsletter, our emails provide you the opportunity to opt out of receiving communications from us. 

## Links

This site contains links to other sites. LuckyVitamin.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

## E-Mails To Customer Service 

We provide email links on our "Customer Services" page that allow you to contact us directly with any questions or comments you may have. We read every message sent in and try to reply promptly to every one. The information you send us is used to respond directly to your questions and comments. We also keep your email correspondence on file so that we may better serve you should you have additional questions in the future. Your personal information is shared with third parties (such as manufacturers) only with your explicit permission.

## Notification of Changes to Privacy Policy

Whenever we change our privacy policy, we will post a notice on our web site indicating that a new version is available. 

## Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: 

LuckyVitamin.com  
Customer Service  
Phone:1-888-635-0474  
Fax: 1-888-635-6190 

Or send us e-mail using the feedback form link on the bottom of every page.
